McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- UA (1973-1977) (Box 66)
  - United Airlines - 1977 1 of 2 (Meredith) (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - UA Meredith 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - United - Flights Attends - Hanlon, Donna - 1976 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines - 1977 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - United - F.A.- Brodigan, Celeste (Bulletin bd.) 4/19/77 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines, 4/20/77, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - UA Paramovie 10/77, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - United - AFA P. Money SF 0-34-77 10/19/77 1 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - United - AFA P. Mooney SFO 34-77 10/19/77 2 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - United - AFA P. Mooney SFO 34-77 10/19/77 3 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - United - AFA - D. Schray, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - United Airlines - 1978 (Compeau) 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - United Airlines 1978 (Compeau) 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - United Airlines 1978 - Prouty (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - United Airlines, 1978 Hines + Bennett (Box 66, Folder 24)
- UA (1978-1979) (Box 67)
  - United Airlines 1978 - Mary Save Stevens - 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - United Airlines - 1978 (Stevens) 2 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines - 1978 (Jackman) 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - United Airlines - 1978 (Jackman) 2 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - UA Burrow 12/15/78, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - UA Burrow 12/15/78, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - UA Burrow 12/15/78, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - UA Burrow 12/15/78, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - UA Burrow 12/15/78, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - UA Burrow 1978 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - UA Webber 4/12/79 1 of 5, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - UA Webber 1979 2 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - UA Webber 1979 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - UA Webber 1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - UA Webber 1979 5 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - UA Webber 1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - United Airlines - 1979 (Steele) 1 of 4 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - United Airlines - 1979 (Steele) 2 of 4 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - United Airlines - 1979 3 of 4 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines - 1979 4 of 4 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - United - 1979 (Traylor) 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - United - 1979 (Traylor) 2 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- UA (1979-1981) (Box 68)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 1 of 8, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 2 of 8, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 3 of 8, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 4 of 8, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 5 of 8, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 6 of 8, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 7 of 8, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - UA MEC 10-79 12-79 Exhibits 8 of 8, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - UA MEC 12-79, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - United - AFA, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 1 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 2 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 3 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 4 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 5 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 6 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - UA 1980 Linneweber 7 of 7 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - UA Morgan 3/29/80 1 of 5, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - UA Morgan 3/29/80 2 of 5, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - UA Morgan 3/29/80 3 of 5, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - UA Morgan 3/29/80 4 of 5, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - UA Morgan 3/29/80 5 of 5, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - United Airlines 1981 - (Sulshi) 1 of 5 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - United Airlines 1981 - (Sulshi) 2 of 5 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - United Airlines 1981 - (Sulshi) 3 of 5 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - United Airlines 1981 - (Sulshi) 4 of 5 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - United Airlines 1981 - (Sulshi) 5 of 5 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - United Airlines 1981 - Usher, Tudyman, White and Apperti 1 of 4 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - United Airlines 1981 - Usher, Tudyman, White and Apperti 2 of 4 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - United Airlines 1981 - Usher, Tudyman, White and Apperti 3 of 4 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - United Airlines 1981 - Usher, Tudyman, White and Apperti 4 of 4 (Box 68, Folder 31)
- UA (1983-1984) (Box 69)
  - UA Olin 1982 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - United Airlines 1983 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - UA 1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - UA System Group 1983 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - UA 1983 System/Group (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - UA System Group 1983 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - UA 1983 System Group (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - UA System Group, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - UA System Group, 1980-1983 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - UA System Group, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - UA Ratchford 4/27/83, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - UA Ratchford, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - UA Ratchford Exhibits 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - UA Ratchford Exhibits 1 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - UA Williams 1/24/83, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - UA 1983 Roth Bill (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - UA - Roth Transcript 1984 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - United Airlines (Case # MEC 3-84) 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - UA (Case # MEC 3-84) 2 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - UA System Group 1983 1 of 7 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - UA System Group 1983 2 of 7, 1983-1985 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - UA System Group 1983 4 of 7, 1983-1985 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - UA System Group 1983, 1983-1985 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - United Airlines -(Case MEC 7-85), 1983-1985 (Box 69, Folder 24)
- UA (1984-1987) (Box 70)
  - UA Wheeler Transcript, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - United - Wheeler '85, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines Dwyer 1986 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - United Dwyer '86, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - United Dwyer 2, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - United Dwyer 3, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - UA Dwyer 1986 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - UA Stearns 7/29/86, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - UA Stearns 1986 Transcript (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - UA Anderson 7/11/86, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines Anderson 7/11/86, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - UA Anderson Transcript, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines Anderson Exhibits, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - United - AFA, 1980-1985 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - UA Anderson Exhibits, 1980-1984 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - UA Anderson Exhibits, 1978-1984 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - United Airlines + AFA 1987 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - UA + AFA 1987 2 of 2 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - UA + AFA Madden 1987 Transcript (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - United - Madden, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - UA Madden 1987 Transcript (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - UA + AFA, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - United Airlines Exhibits, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- UA (cont) - V (Box 71)
  - United Airlines, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - United - Misc., 1978-1982 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - United - Misc., 1977-1983 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - USPS - 1975 -(Marsh) (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - USPS - 1977 (Petite) (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - USPS - 1977 (Berberian) (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - USPS - 1977 (Peters) (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - USPS - 1977 - (Varsege) (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - USPS - 1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - USPS - 1978 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Postal Service - 1978 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - USPS - 1979 - Anderson (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - USPS -, 1977-1979 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Gilmore 8/8/79 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - USPS - 1979 2 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Postal DeLorenzo 1979 1 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Postal DeLorenzo, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Postal DeLorenzo, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Postal DeLorenzo, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Maley 12/19/83 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - US Postal Rural L. Carriers 1983 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - US Postal '85, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Postal 1985 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Postal Service 1987 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - USPS Misc., 1984 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Utica, Products, Inc. Holiday Pay Case, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Veterans Admin. Hosp., 1974 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Vogt Manufacturing Corp., 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 28)
- Wat - Webster (Box 72)
  - Waterloo CSD 1 of 5, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Waterloo CSD 2 of 5, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Waterloo CSD 3 of 5, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Waterloo CSD 4 of 5, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Waterloo CSD 5 of 5, 1972-1974 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Wayne State Univ. '76, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Wayne State + AAUP 12/84 Bills, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman 6/28/85, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Wayne State Reisman Notes 1 of 2, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Wayne State Reisman Notes 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman Exhibits, 1981-1983 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman Exhibits, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman Transcript Vol. 1, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman Vol. 2, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Wayne State U. Reisman Vol. 3, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Wayne State U. Fisher, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Wayne State U. Fisher 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Wayne State U. Fisher Transcript, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Wayne State University Krasner 5/6/87, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Webster CSD 1 of 2, 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Webster CSD 2 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Webster CSD 2/17/81, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Webster CSD, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Webster CSD, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 28)
- West - Z (Box 73)
  - West Irondequoit 1969 1 of 2 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - West Irondequoit 1969 2 of 2 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - West Irondequoit CSD '75, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - WFMJ Broadcasting, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - WGK-TV Corp., 1958-1960 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Wilkinson Trenching Co., 1975 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Winthrop Labs, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - WIXT - Nabet - Syracuse, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - WIXT - Nabet - Syracuse, 1979-1981 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - 66-15 Worthington Corp. General File, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - 66-15 Worthington Corp. General File, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - 66-15 Worthington Corp., 1966 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Worthington Corp. 4/69, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Worthington, Compressor + Engine Div. 1969 1 of 4 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Worthington, Compressor + Engine Div. 1969 3 of 4 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Worthington, Compressor + Engine Div. 1969 4 of 4 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Worthington Compressors Inc. '76, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Worthington Corp. + OPEIU Local 212, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Yates County + CSEA 1 of 5 1985 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Yates 1985 2 of 5 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Yates 1985 3 of 5 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Yates 1985 4 of 5 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Yates 1985 5 of 5 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Misc. "Uncorrected" Arb. Awards - '75-'76, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Misc. "Uncorrected Arb. Awards" '75-'76, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Misc. "Uncorrected" Arb. Awards '76-'77, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Misc. "Unconnected" Arb. Awards '76-'77, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Misc. "Unconnected" Arb. Awards - '77-'78, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Misc. "Unconnected" Arb. Awards - '77-78, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Misc. "Uncorrected" Arb. Awards '78-'79, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Misc. "Uncorrected" Arb. Awards - '78-'79, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 31)
- Case #s 70-3 - 73-18 (Box 74)
  - 70-3 70-4, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 70-6, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 70-8, 1970-1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 70-9, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 70-10 70-11, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 70-12, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 70-13, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - 70-14 70-15, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 70-16, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - 71-1 71-2 71-3, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - 71-4 71-5, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - 71-6, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - 71-7 71- 8 71-9, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - 71-10, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - 71-11 71-12, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - 71-13 71-14, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - 71-15 71-16, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - 71-17 71-18, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - 71-19, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - 71-19(2), 1972 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - 71-20 71-21, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - 72-1, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - 72-2(1), 1972 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - 72-2(2), 1972 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - 72-3, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - 72-4, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - 72-5, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - 72-6, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - 72-7 72-8, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - 72-9 72-10, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - 72-11 72-12, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - 72-14 72-15, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - 72-16 72-17, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - 72-19 72-21, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - 73-1, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - 73-2, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - 73-3, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - 73-4, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - 73-5 73-6, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - 73-7, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - 73-8, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - 73-10 73-13, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - 73-14(1), 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - 73-14(2), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - 73-14(3), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 45)
  - 73-14(4), 1976 (Box 74, Folder 46)
  - 73-15 73-16 73-17, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 47)
  - 73-18(1), 1976 (Box 74, Folder 48)
  - 73-18(2), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 48)
- Case #s 73-19 - 77-10 (Box 75)
  - 73-19 Thru 72-25, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - 73-26(1), 1974-1975 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - 73-26(2), 1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 73-27(1), 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 73-27(2), 1974 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - 73-28 73-29, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - 74-1, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - 74-2 74-5 74-6, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - 74-9 74-10 74-11, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - 74-12, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - 74-15, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - 74-20, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - 74-24, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - 74-25, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - 74-26, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - 74-28, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - 75-3 75-6, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - 75-7(1), 1975 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - 75-7(2), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - 75-8 75-9, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - 75-13, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - 75-14, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - 75-17 75-19 75-23 75-25 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - 75-28 75-31 75-32, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - 75-33 75-35, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - 75-36, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - 75-37, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - 75-38(1), 1975 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - 75-38(2), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - 75-39, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - 75-40, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - 75-41, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - 75-42, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - 76-6 76-4, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - 76-7 (1), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - 76-7 (2), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - 76-9 (1), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - 76-9(2), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - 76-9(3), 1976 (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - 76-10, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - 76-12, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - 76-14, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - 76-15, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - 76-17 76-18 76-19 76-21 76-24 (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - 76-26 76-28 76-31, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 45)
  - 76-32 76-36 76-37, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - 76-38, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - 76-49 76-56, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 48)
  - 76-59, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 49)
  - 77-5(1), 1977 (Box 75, Folder 50)
  - 77-5(2), 1977 (Box 75, Folder 51)
  - 77-10, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 52)
- Case #s 77-10(a) - 78-32 (Box 76)
  - 77-10(a), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - 77-10(a), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 77-10(a), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 77-10(a), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 77-11(1), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 77-11(2), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - 77-13, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - 77-18(1), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - 77-18(2), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - 77-22(1), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - 77-22(2), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - 77-22(3), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - 77-26, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - 77-29 (1), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - 77-29(2), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - 77-30, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - 77-31, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - 77-32+33, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - 77-36, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - 77-37, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - 77-38, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - 77-39, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - 77-40, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - 77-41, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - 77-46, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - 77-47, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - 77-48 77-49, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - 77-53 77-56, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - 77-60, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - 77-64 77-70 77-71 77-77, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - 77-78, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - 77-79, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - 77-86 77-88, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - 78-1, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - 78-4(1), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - 78-4(2), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - 78-5, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - 78-9, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - 78-18, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - 78-23 78-24, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - 78-24(a), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - 78-27 78-29, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - 78-32(1), 1979 (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - 78-32(2), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - 78-32(3), 1979 (Box 76, Folder 45)
- Case #s 78-32 - 79-64 (Box 77)
  - 78-37, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - 78-40, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 78-42, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 78-42(1), 1970-1977 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - 78-44 78-49, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - 78-50, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - 78-51, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - 78-56, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - 78-58, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - 78-59(b), 1980 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - 78-62, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - 78-65, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - 78-67, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - 78-68(a), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - 78-80(1), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - 78-80(2), 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - 78-84, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - 78-86, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - 78-100, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - 79-3, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - 79-4, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - 79-5, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - 79-16 79-18, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - 79-20, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - 79-25, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - 79-27, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - 79-29, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - 79-38(1), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - 79-38(2), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - 79-41(1), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - 79-41(2), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - 79-42(a) 79-43(a), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - 79-45, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - 79-47, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - 79-50(a), 1980 (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - 79-51, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - 79-53, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - 79-54, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - 79-56, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - 79-57, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - 79-60(1), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - 79-60(2), 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 42)
  - 79-61, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 43)
  - 79-62, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 44)
  - 79-64, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 45)
- Case #s 79-65 - 80-56 (Box 78)
  - 79-65(1), 1980 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - 79-65(2), 1980 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - 79-65, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - 79-67, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - 79-7235, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 79-7300, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - 79-73(a), 1980 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - 79-74, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - 79-75, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - 79-76, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - 79-80, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - 79-81, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - 79-84, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - 79-85 79-86 79-87, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - 79-88, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - 79-97, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - 79-98, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - 79-99, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - 79-100, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - 79-102, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - 79-106, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - 79-107, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - 79-107(a), 1980 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - 79-110, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - 79-112, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - 79-120, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - 79-123, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - 80-5, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - 80-9, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - 80-10, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - 80-11, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - 80-12 80-17, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - 80-14, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - 80-18, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - 80-20, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - 80-21, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - 80-23, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - 80-28, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - 80-30, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - 80-31, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - 80-34, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - 80-35 80-36, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - 80-37, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - 80-38, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - 80-39(a), 1981 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - 80-40, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - 80-41, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - 80-43 80-44, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 48)
  - 80-45, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 49)
  - 80-52, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - 80-52(a), 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 51)
  - 80-53, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 52)
  - 80-54, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 53)
  - 80-56, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 54)
- Case #s 80-57 - 81-142 (Box 79)
  - 80-57, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - 80-59, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - 80-61 80-62, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - 80-68, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - 80-76, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - 81-1 81-16, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - 81-2, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - 81-3, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - 81-5(b), 1981 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - 81-7(a), 1981 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - 81-8, 1978-1981 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - 81-11, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - 81-12, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - 81-13, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - 81-17, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - 81-19, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - 81-21, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - 81-22, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - 81-23, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - 81-25, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - 81-29, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - 81-30, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - 81-33, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - 81-34, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - 81-36, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - 81-37, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - 81-38, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - 81-39, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - 81-41, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - 81-42, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - 81-46, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - 81-47, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - 81-48, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - 81-51, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - 81-52, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - 81-53(1), 1982 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - 81-53(2), 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - 81-56, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - 81-57, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - 81-58, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - 81-59, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - 81-60, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - 81-61 81-62 81-68, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - 81-63, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - 81-65, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - 81-66, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - 81-68, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - 81-72, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - 81-75, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - 81-76 81-77, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - 81-78, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - 81-80, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - 81-83, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - 81-84, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - 81-86, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - 81-88, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - 81-91, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - 81-94, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - 81-99, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 59)
  - 81-100 81-103, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - 81-101 (a), 1981 (Box 79, Folder 61)
  - 81-105, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 62)
  - 81-112, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 63)
  - 81-113, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 64)
  - 81-114, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - 81-119, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 66)
  - 81-121 81-122, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 67)
  - 81-126, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 68)
  - 81-130, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 69)
  - 81-131, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 70)
  - 81-134 81-135, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 71)
  - 81-137, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 72)
  - 81-140, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 73)
  - 81-142, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 74)
- Case #s 81-143 - 82-145 (Box 80)
  - 81-143, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - 81-147, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - 81-150, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - 81-154, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 4)